[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Syria"]}, "docId": "130829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 34, "question": "Why are you so critical of the president's actions so far in relation to Syria?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 35, "answer": "Well, first of all, we have watched the Syria evolve into one of the great humanitarian tragedies in recent history.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Syria"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Middle East"]}, "docId": "130829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "NNPS", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "WRB", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "VBG", "CC", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "VB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ":", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 53, "question": "How did you get around that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 54, "answer": "Well, first of all I think it's understandable that Americans are very skeptical and cynical and that's why the actions that we should have been taking and should still be taking have to be explained to the American people and the consequences of widespread conflict -- regional conflict in the Middle East.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "CD", "NNS", ",", "IN", "POS", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 128, "question": "Is that the position you take in?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 129, "answer": "I've only taken it for two years, that's fairly well- known and the fact is when we haven't the situation has deteriorated in the numbers and the tragedies that I just described to you have taken place.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "IN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", ":", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 141, "question": "What is your reaction?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 142, "answer": "Well, I think that we do have a situation, what that calls for some very, very serious consideration for -- of our options.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "130829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 155, "question": "Is it America's place anymore in the modern world now to be getting involved in other country's civil wars?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 156, "answer": "Well, I think it's America's place to show leadership in resolving some of these very, very difficult and dangerous situations and you do that in a number of ways.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["United States"], "LOCATION": ["United States"], "PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "130829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "MD", "VB", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "CC", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 194, "question": "General Hayden the problem is no one's quite sure what the plan is and President Obama hasn't committed yet to what the plan may be and that plan may now have to dramatically change if British forces will not be involved and that sets a bandwagon running around say, the French and other internal forces he said, \"Look, we just can't take part in this,\" would America consider unilateral military action under those circumstances and how risky is that to America's interest?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "NN", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "TO", "WP", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "CC", "IN", "NN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNS", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "CC", "IN", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "``", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "''", "MD", "NNP", "VB", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "IN", "TO", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 195, "answer": "No, I think the United States would act unilaterally because President Obama made this commitment for the United States and frankly for himself personally about a year ago.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Hayden", "Obama"], "LOCATION": ["America", "America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Administration"]}, "docId": "130829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 201, "question": "What does that lead him politically and what would you think is the sensible course of action now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "CC", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 202, "answer": "Well, this is an enormous set back for the Administration.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Assad"]}, "docId": "130829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "RB", "TO", "WP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 242, "question": "How dangerous would that be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "MD", "IN", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 243, "answer": "It's quite dangerous and it's a separable choice from responding appropriately to what Assad has done with chemical weapons.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Tuesday"], "TIME": ["night"]}, "docId": "130829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "VBN", "NNS", "CC", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 249, "question": "But if you are President Obama, what do you do and how soon do you do it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "CC", "WRB", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 250, "answer": "Well this is the problem, I mean he's going to the G20 group of industrialized nations and for major consultations leaving Tuesday night.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "NN", "POS", "NN", ",", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "CD", "IN", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "CC", "DT", "VBZ", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "RB", "RB", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 272, "question": "Why do we fear them so much?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 273, "answer": "I mean chemical weapons there's all sorts of different types of them, but in this particular case, you're right we're talking about something let's say, particularly chilling these neurotoxic agents and in this case the belief is that sarin which is probably one of the most toxic chemical weapons out there that's been used in warfare is what they suspect it is and this is something they can test for pretty easily up here.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "RB", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", ",", "CC", "NN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "POS", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 278, "question": "And Sanjay, from all of the video evidence that you've seen some awful images of young kids being slaughtered and so on, does it look to you like the side effects of a sarin attack or something very similar?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", "VBN", "CC", "RB", "IN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 279, "answer": "I think so, you know, it's tough to sometimes make, you know, make conclusions from that video evidence alone, but hearing some of the doctors' descriptions of these in some of these camps and the doctors without boarders over there.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sanjay"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "RB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "NNS", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 301, "question": "Are they sensible to try and do what they're doing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 302, "answer": "No, and you know, Piers it's sad actually to watch that because I mean I -- people think -- they may think that they're protecting themselves in some way and it's sad because maybe that's the only thing that they have.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 339, "question": "What do you think of what she said?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 340, "answer": "It was rather astonishing and I gratefully spoke with you about this once already.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 408, "question": "Is there anything wrong inherently about her behavior?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "NN", "JJ", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 409, "answer": "Right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]